片名：高原漂流
拉高镇
Lets go, Buster.
出发，老伙计
Beer.
And a bottle.
啤酒，另加一瓶
Aint much good.
全在这里了，这些酒不太好
Its all there is.
Will you want anything else?
还要些什么？
Just a peaceful hour to drink it in.
只想安安静静地喝杯酒
Flea-bitten range bums dont usually stop in Lago.
跳蚤、流氓是不会在拉高逗留的
Life heres a little too quick for em.
他们在这里命也不会长
Maybe you thinkyoure fast enough to keep up with us, huh?
你以为可以跟上我们的步伐吗?
A lot faster than youll ever live to be.
我会比你快得多
Yes, sir?
先生
A shave and a hot bath?
我要刮胡子和洗个热水浴
Thatll be 90 cents.
要收九角钱
Cash.
要现金，我意思是…
What I mean to say is that the 90 cents usually comes fi rst...
通常要先付九角钱
but, hell, it dont really matter.
但不要紧，迟付早付也没分别
Before or after, whats the diff?
Eau de lilacs only ten cents more.
用丁香香水要多加一角钱
Lilac water. The ladies love it.
女士喜欢丁香香水
Shall we make it an even dollar? No.
合计整整一块钱，好吗？不？
Right you are, gentlemen.
先生们，请自便，随便坐
Be right with you. Just have a chair.
You dont like our company?
你不喜欢我们这伙人吗？
Whats the matter with you?
你有什么问题？
Im speakin?to you, pig shit.
我在跟你说话！猪猡
I think hes got some ofthat pig shit in his ear.
我看他耳朵被猪屎塞了
I dont know which smells worse, him or the shit in the bottle.
不知何者较臭呢？
是他还是瓶里的垃圾呢？
What did you say your name was again?
你刚才说你叫什么名字？
I didnt.
我没说
No. I guess you didnt at that, did you?
我猜你从没尝过雪茄，是吗？
Why dont you watch where youre going? Look at this. Its ruined.
你走路要小心点
你看，都弄坏了
Theres no need for all that.
你根本不必做这一切
All what?
一切什么？
Ifyou want to get acquainted, why dont you just say so?
你想结识我，何不直言呢？
Acquainted?
结识你？
Youd be amusing ifyou werent so pathetic!
你是扮同情还是扮风趣？
Just a minute. Im not fi nished with you yet.
等一下，我还没说完
At a distance, youd almost pass for a man.
远看你也算是个男子汉
But youre certainly a disappointment up close, arent you?
但近观你却令人很失望
To your feet, maam. Theyre almost as big as your mouth.
你的脚差不多像你的嘴般大
You know what you are?
知否你是什么？ 什么？
Just trash.
只不过是垃圾
A bottle ofwhiskey for courage and the manners ofa goat.
你借酒壮胆，其实胆小如羔羊
Youre the one who could use a lesson in manners.
你应该去学习礼貌
Not from you, whiskey breath.
但不会向你学，酒鬼
Let go of me.
放我走！…不！放我走
Let go!
Let go of me!
放我走！你…
放低我！不…你想怎样？
Put me down!
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
My horse.
我的马
A room.
要一间房间
Would you like to register, please, sir?
请先登记，先生
Somebody, please help me. Help me!
来人！救我呀！
Damn you all to hell!
你们去死吧！
- Good morning. Sleep well? - Yeah.
早安，睡得好吗？ 好
Say, are you planning to stay, keep your room another night?
你打算保留房间，多住一晚吗？
- Ill let you know. - All right. Anything you say.
我会通知你的
好的，随便你
Mornin?
早安
- Ive still got a bath coming. - Hot bath comin?right up. Yes, sir.
我来洗澡
要个舒适的热水浴，好的
Put some more hot water in that tub. This gentleman wants a bath.
摩迪加，放多点热水进浴缸
这位先生想沐浴
You can hang your clothes right down there on the peg.
你可将衣服挂在绳上
- Miss Peekins does a nice-- Im sorry. - Right this way, captain, sir.
庇坚丝小姐精于…噢！对不起
Unlessn you want Mordecai to take em out while youre soakin?..
先生，这边走
你沐浴时可叫摩迪加洗衣服
Miss Peekins does a right clean boiled wash.
庇坚丝精于替人洗热水浴
Uses lye for pants rabbits, she does. No itch, no scratch.
她会用润滑露，不会令你很痒
Pour the water, Mordecai, before it gets cold.
摩迪加，趁热将水倒进浴缸
We want the gentleman to be comfortable.
我要这位男士舒适的享受
Ive been wantin?to talk to you.
我一直想跟你谈谈
I might as well get this stool here...
and set right down and do it, huh?
我去拿张椅子坐下跟你谈
Ifthats all right with you, huh?
你会同意吧
What its about is Billy Borders.
是关于比利波达的
Dont know the man.
我不认识这人
You missed your chance, cause you shot him yesterday.
你错过机会了，因你昨天枪杀他
Him and lke Sharp and Fred Morris.
他、伊梳茨以及法列摩利士
You know, those isjust the names in case youre interested.
只是些名字，你有兴趣知吗？
Well, lm not really interested, Sheriff.
我没兴趣
I cant say I blame you.
我并非要怪责你
Billy, he wasnt a loved man, no.
比利，他不得人心
He didnt have much personality. What he did have was all bad, just bad.
也没有人格
他所做的尽是坏事
What youre tryin?to say is theres no charge, right?
你是说，不会起诉我？
创Forgive and forget.创 Thats our motto.
“宽恕与不追究”是我们的格言
You dirty bastard!
你这杂种！
Ill kill you!
我要杀死你
Damn it, Callie!
妈的！歌莉…妈的！
- Callie, damn it! - Let go of me, you fat lug!
停手放开我
Stop-- Ouch!
Tell him ld appreciate it...
你去求他，待我谈完才离开本镇
if he doesnt leave town until I talk to him.
Goddamn it!
Ill kill you!
我要杀死他
I wonder why it took her so long to get mad?
我奇怪什么事令她那么愤怒？
Because maybe you didnt go back for more.
可能因为你不再去找她
It dont seem to me that we got a choice.
看来我们别无选择了
Seein?we got no time to send for help...
已经没有时间派人去求救
and further seein?that our sheriffs about as much use...
况且警长想以牙还牙对付他们
as tits on a boar.
Sorry lm late. Anything happen?
对不起，我迟到了，何事
No, no. His Honours had the floor.
不，大人事忙
In case you hadnt heard, Stacey Bridges and the Carlin brothers...
可能你未收到消息
- are due to get out ofjail today. - They comin?here?
史达斯及卡连兄弟今天将出狱
Thats their plan according to reports. No reason to believe theyve changed it.
他们会来这里？
据报告他们计划到来，事在必行
Possibly theyve repented their ways.
他们可能来忏悔哩
Preacher, theyre gonna burn this town to the ground, and you know it.
教士，他们会令本镇永无宁日
What were talking about now is a way to stop them.
我们开会是想办法阻止他们
Weve got to fi nd that way now, and quick.
要尽快想个办法
Nevertheless, my conscience will not allow me to be a party...
我的良知不容许我参与
to the hiring ofa professional gunfi ghter.
雇用一个职业枪手去对付他们
Maybe youd like to go out there and stand them offyourself, Preacher.
你自己去制止他们吧
Im just a simple man of God.
我只是由天主差遣的一个普通人
Its time we unsimplified you, Reverend.
到时候令你变得不普通了
Borders, Morris and Short were professional gunfi ghters...
波达、摩利士和梳茨是职业枪手
on the payroll ofthe Lago Mining Company...
受雇于拉高矿产 保护我们的利益
to protect our interests and the interests ofthis town...
which are identical.
以及本镇的共同利益
They stood around drinking beer and looking snotty for a full year.
他们一年来只会高傲地闲逛喝酒
Then one day before we actually needed the bastards...
当我们需要他们地时候
they managed to get themselves killed.
他们竟然自寻死路
So ifyouve got a suggestion, wed be delighted to hear it.
若你由建议，我们乐于聆听
Otherwise, take your conscience elsewhere...
否则收起你的良知，再想办法
while we think about saving your ass.
Land sakes! Wheres time gone to?
时光飞逝
Miss Peekins?eldest is feeling poorly. I promised--
我忘记了可怜地庇坚丝老太太
Ifyou gentlemen will excuse me?
各位，请恕我失陪
Well, we were talkin? about hirin?a gunfi ghter.
我们刚谈到雇用枪手
But we dont know anything about that fella there.
对，我们对那人一无所知
We know he took the best we could fi nd to hire like Grant took Vicksburg.
我只知他是最理想的人选
Yeah, with a hidden gun in his lap.
手枪藏在腿侧
Three for three. One right between the eyes!
三发三中，一枪射中双眼中间
Goddamnedest shooting I ever even heard of.
从没见过如此准确的枪法
I still say were asking for trouble!
我仍坚持，我们是自找麻烦
What do we know about him? Who is he? Where does he come from?
如此粗人，我们了解他吗？
Youve got our permission to go and ask him.
他是谁？来自何方？
我们批准你去问他
Although the last three that tried that didnt fare all that well.
虽然上次那三个人不太理想…
Let me out!
Damn you!
Let go of me, you fat slug!
Let go of me! Get off me!
Hey, come here. What is this?
过来，什么事？
I wasjust down there soundin?out that stranger...
我正在赞扬那神秘客
- when she come in blastin?away like-- - All right, Sam.
而你竟然进来喧哗…
我知道了
Youre gonna let him get away with this?
你打算让他到来为非作歹？
- Be a little patient, will ya? - Patient?
可否忍耐一下？ 忍耐？
When a mans used to having his own way...
歌莉，要应付习惯独断独行的人
you let him have it until he goes too far.
要让他自由发挥，除非他太过份
Just what do you consider goin?too far?
你认为怎样才算是过份？
Isnt forcible rape in broad daylight a misdemeanour in this town?
光天化日在市内强奸算是过份吗
Theres too much at stake to throw away on hysterics now.
到处歇斯底里地呼喊是过份吗？
Hysterics?
歇斯底里？
I can remember some hysterics one night not too long ago.
我记得最近由一晚会歇斯底里
Callie, keep your mouth shut!
歌莉，你闭嘴
Morgan, get her out of here.
摩根，将她赶出去
Ill see you later.
我迟些找你
Not while that squinty-eyed son ofa bitch is still breathing!
那贱人活着，你休想找我
You wonder iftheres a man left in this town!
你容许镇内由一个男人…
I mean, one honest-to-God man with a full set of balls!
一个完全合作， 忠于主地男人吗
Well...
why not?
为何不肯？
Cause lm not a gunfi ghter.
因我不是枪手
Well, dont get fact mixed up with stupid.
别将愚昧行为与事实混淆
Besides, I have nothing against these men.
此外，我跟那班人没有过节
Whod you say they are?
你们所说的是什么人？
Stacey Bridges and his cousins, the Carlin boys.
是史达斯和他的侄儿卡连兄弟
They worked for the company.
他们替公司工作
What you call 创troubleshooters.创
是你所谓的麻烦枪手
Just like those three you done in yesterday...
他们跟你昨天所杀的那三个人 一样
except when they was here before, there was lots oftrouble.
分别在于他们到来前有很多麻烦
And they took care of it too...
但他们应付自如
except they got too damn big for their britches.
可惜他们架势凌人
Started pushin?people around and takin?over the town...
开始欺凌百姓
- and we had to-- - Had to what?
到处抢掠，因此我们必须…
必须什么？
We had to take them into custody, thats what.
必须监管他们，情况便是这样
I clapped the old bracelets on them myself.
然后呢？
我亲自用手铐扣押他们
Hey, you wont be wantin? that slab of pie, will ya?
你不想吃吗？
You know what happened, friend?
朋友，你知道发生了什么事情吗？
They stole a golden ingot out ofthe mining office...
他们在探矿公司偷了一块金
and they hid it under the floorboard ofthe shack that they lived in.
他们太大意了，是吗？
Kind ofcareless ofem, wasnt it?
Does a mining company usually leave gold ingots lyin?around like that?
探矿公司会随便放金块的吗？
That does seem a bit peculiar.
此事有蹊跷
Matter offact, Stacey kept bringing that up at the trial all the time...
史达斯在审讯时不断提出这问题
saying that he was being railroaded.
他说是被人引诱犯罪的
Thats why theyre mad at us.
知否他们为何恼我们？
-Ill tell you what you can do, Sheriff. -What?
我现在可教你应怎办
When those boys come back to town...
怎么办？
当他们回到镇内… 怎样？
you just clap the bracelets right on em.
你只需将他们扣上手铐 我
Me?
对 我忘记告诉你
I might have forgot to mention...
they were all three passed out at the time.
他们三人同时间出狱
Look, lm no lawman.
我其实不懂法律
Theyjust hung this thing on me...
只是人们将责任交给我
when that young Marshal Duncan was killed.
当年邓肯警长被杀
You know he was whipped to death right here in this street.
他是在这条街上被鞭打致死的
Bullwhipped. Damnedest thing I ever saw.
疯狂地鞭打我从未见过如此残酷
Why would anybody want to do a thing like that?
为什么所有人也这样做？
I dont know. It wasnt anybody from this town anyhow.
我不知，他们不是本镇的人
How do you know?
你怎知道？
This is a good town and these are good people.
这只是个民风朴素的小镇
Look, friend, we sure would like it ifyoud help us with our problem.
你替我们解决问题后…
你定会喜欢这镇
Only problem youve got is a short supply of guts.
警长，你的问题是欠缺胆量
You people dont need me.
你们其实可不需要我
Look.
你看
Place a couple of good riflemen on top ofthat building.
可安排两个长枪手站在屋顶
Maybe a couple more with shotguns down behind grain bags over there.
或者再多两个持手枪者在下面
A few more on this roof here. A lookout up there in the tower.
派人在楼顶监视
Maybe a rifleman. That should take care of it.
或者可用长枪手，便可解决一切
Well, what would it take to see that through?
你知否此举所费不菲
The ambush. What would it cost us?
派人埋伏要花很多钱
Sheriff, I dont know if I really like this town that much.
警长，我真的不太喜欢这镇
This is a God-fearin?town.
为什么？这镇的人民都敬畏主
These are God-fearin?people.
You like em, you save em.
你爱他们便要拯救他们
What ifwe offered you anything you want?
我们愿意接受你的任何要求
Anything?
任何要求？
Unlimited credit. Thats what it means.
是无限量的贷款
An open charge account with no reckonin?
是一个免还款的户口
What His Honours trying to say is...
他的意思是…
you got yourself a free hand in this town.
你在镇内可全无限制
- Any damn thing I want, huh? - Yeah. Go on. Help yourself.
我可以提任何要求？
对，请自便，这是我的荣幸
Help yourself! Go ahead. Its my pleasure.
Yes, sir. Anything you want thats here...
你有什么需要
as best as we can get it foryou, we will.
我们会尽力而为去满足你
Even if its some little squaw or Mex...
甚至租墨西哥或印第安女子…
to keep your bed warm at night.
替你暖床，我们也愿意
Hey, you!
唏！你！
Keep your sticky fi ngers off them blankets...
不是光顾便不要碰！
and keep them kids under control.
好好看管你两个孩子
Goddamn savages.
妈的！生蕃！
And besides, about handlin?that ambush...
此外，关于埋伏一事
everybody in town, more or less, is at your orders.
全镇的人也可由你指派
Here you go.
拿去 不！…
- No, no. - Tell him its all right.
告诉他，没问题
Its all right.
没问题了
Anything I want, huh?
任何我想要的？
Hows that feel?
你觉得怎样？
Not bad. Ill take em.
不错，我要拿走它
All right, thats three pairs of hand-stitched boots...
三对手造的皮靴…
and a tooled belt with silver buckle.
一条银扣的皮带…
Thatll be-- five and two, carry the nine--
是五元二角，再加九角
that comes to exactly--
总数是… 不准收钱
No charge.
Come on, now.
来吧
Id like to get all these people a drink.
我想请所有人饮酒
Yes, sir. One round for the house. There you are.
好的，每人一杯入酒吧帐
This gentleman heres buying a round for the house.
这位男士请全场人饮酒
No fair. I ordered one too. Dont I get a glass of beer?
不公平，我已叫了， 可有一杯吗
You get a glass of beer right there. Coming up.
你的啤酒在这里，来了
There we are.
Now, thats one round for the house, sir. Anything else?
这一轮是酒吧请的，还要什么？
Get yourselfsomething.
你可自己挑选喜欢的
Thankyou very kindly, sir. Ill have a cigar.
你真好人，我要支雪茄
And smoke it later.
迟些才抽
Now, including the smoke, that comes to about $8.50.
连这雪茄，合共八元五角
Theres no charge, Lutie.
鲁提，不准收钱
You was at the meeting. Anything he wants in this town, he gets.
你也有参加会议的
- You voted on it. - I didnt know that meant free whiskey.
他可在镇内得到想要的东西
而你也投票赞成
我不知会有免费威士忌的
Everybodys got to put somethin?in the kitty. Right?
所有人也获得心爱的东西吗？
Right.
对
About time this town had a new sheriff.
是时候替小镇选个新警长了
Im the sheriff? lm the sheriff!
我是警长…
Im sorry, Sam...
森，对不起，你发育不良
but you looked so comical when he put your badge on the runt.
你配上徽章太滑稽了
Im not a runt anymore. Im the sheriff.
我并非发育不良，我是警长
- And the mayor. - And lm the mayor.
亦是镇长 我亦是镇长
- Any objections? - No. No, thats fi ne.
有反对吗？
没有，就这样吧
Im the mayor. Im the sheriff.
我是警长，我是镇长
No more 创Mordecai, bring the water.
不再需要换水洗衣服及做杂务
Mordecai, take the laundry. Clean up the mess.创
Hot damn! lm gonna declare a holiday.
我要宣布今天是假期
Hot damn!
Wait a minute.
等等…
I cant be a sheriff if I dont have a gun.
我没有配枪怎能当警长
Is this about the size gun youre lookin?for?
你想这哦这般大小的手枪吗？
No, that one. Thatll do.
不，这支，这支可以了
Whatever this gent wants, hes to have.
这位男士想要什么也可得到
Orders of Mr Drake and Mr Allen.
这是狄克和阿伦定了的
I want every man in the regiment to have one ofthese nice rifles.
我希望军团每人个也有支长枪
What regiment?
什么军团？
- The City of Lago Volunteers. - Never heard ofem.
是拉高镇义勇军团
You ought to. Youre in it.
从没听过
So are you, you and all ofyou out there.
真风趣，你身为一份子也不知
你也是，你们所有人出去
I want you all out in the street in ten minutes for drill.
我要所有人十分钟内到街上操练
Well, thats that.
Bridges, you Carlin boys...
史达斯，卡连兄弟
dont forget your tickets back here to my little hotel.
别忘记有空再回来我这小酒店
And dont worry-- they aint loaded.
别担心，是没上膛的
What about our horses?
我们的马呢 我们有三匹良驹
We had three good animals.
What do you thinkyouve been eatin? the last six months?
你们过去六个月吃的是什么？
Damn him! I didnt eat my own horse!
操他！
我们没有吃自己的马
That slop he fed us wasnt our horses. Hejust stole em and sold em!
那些食物并非用我们的马做的
他只不过偷去马匹卖给别人
- Shut up. - Thats what he done!
是他做的 闭嘴
When we get to Lago, you can have the mayors horse.
去拉高镇便可得到镇长的马
Fried or barbecued.
要煎要烤也可以
Well, I guess we walk some.
我们步行吧
Old Drake and Allen dont seem to have remembered.
狄克和阿伦可能忘记了
Theyll remember.
他们会记得的
One way or another, theyll remember.
无论如何，也会记得的
All right.
好了
You dont want to get shot.
你想受到枪击
You dont want your shops or houses burned.
或是房屋被烧毁
You dont want your women touched. You dont want anything to happen.
妻子被人侵犯，常有事发生
Except youre afraid to do anything about it.
皆因你们怯于反抗
Oryou dont know how.
或是不懂怎去做
Shit!
妈的！
Fire!
I dont remember lending my wagons to be shot up...
我竟借出马车让他们乱枪扫射
by those goddamned fools out there.
Youre gonna look awfully silly with that knife sticking up your ass.
你真蠢，利刀会伤你屁股的
Fire! Pull those triggers! Come on!
You still here?
你要留在这里？
No, I wasjust goin?
不，我正打算走
- Damn! Can you do that every time? - Damn right he can.
妈的！你每次也射的中？
Were not gonna have a thing in the world to worry about.
对，一定的
那么，不必担心了，就当去旅行
This is gonna be a picnic!
All right, keep em after it, huh?
好了，追赶他们
You men carpenters?
你是个木匠吗？
S? senor. We do rough fixings.
是，我们做粗糙的木工
Could you make some big tables that a lot of people could sit?
你去做些大台子，足够很多人坐的
- Like for a church picnic? - Exactly.
像教会用的台？ 完全一样
Well, you could use sawhorses and one-by-twelvers.
可用锯床做，一张可坐很多人
Could you have them ready for me by tomorrow morning?
可否明早之前完成？
- Ifwe have the lumber. - Youll have the lumber.
有木材吗？ 有，跟我来
Come on with me.
- You really plannin?a picnic? - Any objection?
你真的要去野餐？ 有反对吗？
No, just its the damnedest thing I ever heard of.
不，只是未听过如此古怪的意见
- You havent heard the funny part. - Whats that?
你没听到有趣的部分 是什么
Youre furnishing the beer and whiskey.
你负责供应啤酒、威士忌
- Preacher. - Good morning, Brother Belding.
教士
- Mrs Lake wasjust asking about you. - How is the dear old soul?
早安，贝登兄弟
力克太太刚提起你
Shes chipper as a jaybird. I dont know how she does it.
那老人家怎么了？
她弱的像垂死之鸟，怎能活下去
Shes got the strength of her faith, Brother Belding.
她怀着信念支持下去
Praise God. The strength of her faith.
要多谢主赐给她信念
Too bad about your barn. Termites?
你的牛棚被白蚁蛀吗？
Theres nothing wrong with my barn. Its sound as a dollar.
不，它很坚固
How come those two Mexs is tearin?it down?
为什么那两个墨西哥人要拆掉它
What?
什么？
What do you greasy bastards thinkyoure doing to my barn?
你们两个为何拆我牛棚？
Exactly what I told em.
是我叫他们拆的
Were requisitioning your barn, Belding.
贝登，我们要借用你的牛棚
Any objection?
有反对吗？
You men can go back to work.
你们可继续工作
Would you mind tellin?me what the hells goin?on here?
你介意告诉我你想做什么吗？
You can help out too.
你也可帮忙的
You want me to help you tear down my barn?
你要我帮手拆毁自己的牛棚？
Wait a minute.
等等…
Maybe hed be better use if hed help us collect...
最好叫他去收集欠缺的项目
the few little items were still missing.
Items? What items? What for?
我？项目？什么项目？
You got the list, Sheriff. Read it to him.
你有清单，警长，你讲给他听
We still need 35 bedsheets...
仍欠三十五张床单
one barbecued steer...
一只烤可的小牛，二百加仑红油
and 200 gallons of red paint.
Red paint?
红油？
Were counting on you for the bedsheets.
我们靠你去张罗床单
- Is there anything else? - Yes, there is.
还有其他吗？ 有
How longs it gonna take you to get everybody out ofyour hotel?
要花多久才能叫你酒店的住客来
- What? - Everybody out.
什么？
- How long is it gonna take? - I just cant--
所有人到来，要花多少时间？
I got eight people living in rooms up there in my hotel.
我不能，我酒店住了八个人
Where are they gonna go?
我不知道他们去了哪里？
Out.
出来
You know bettern to walk in a mans camp and--
最好不要走入男人的营内
What the hell is goin?on?
究竟发生什么事？
Well, Stacey, it looks like we got three fresh horses.
史达斯，我们会有三匹新鲜的马
Wait a while.
等一会
Hes got him some snappy duds.
要替他找个伴
Faster!
快点
Fire! Pull that trigger!
- Any improvement? - Some.
有改善吗？ 一点点
Lew and I were thinking. Maybe we were hasty in our decision.
我在想，我们的决定可能太仓促
What do you mean?
你是什么意思？
Maybe we dont need any outside help to solve our problem.
我们不应借助外力去解决问题
Hell, Dave, maybe we dont even have a problem.
或许我们根本没有问题
Every man that ever got sent up...
所有被派出差的人也跑回来
went away saying hed come back and get even, right?
说宁愿回来，保持原状
But can you actually remember anyone ever comin?back and doin?anything?
你记得有没有人会成功地回来？
I cant think ofone. Can you?
我一个也记不起，你呢？
You want to get rid ofthe gunfi ghter, is that it?
你意思是想赶走那神枪手？
Dave, weve got to before its too late.
我们要趁早赶走他
Hes making a mock ofthis whole town.
他要全镇人模拟战争
Making that little dwarf the sheriff.
他叫那侏儒警长…
Kickin?my own people out of my own hotel.
将我酒店的租客赶出酒店
Got halfofthe women in town sewing bedsheets together.
要镇内半数妇女缝合床单
Got those Mexicans down there building long picnic tables.
那些床单亦属于我的
Lutie Naylor barbecuin? a whole damn steer.
叫那些墨西哥人做野餐台
- Some kind ofa picnic. - Right here in our own town.
要虞迪烧烤小牛，要去野餐般
- Sounds pretty good to me. - What do you mean?
这一切全在我们镇内搞
似乎是个好主意 什么意思
It sounds like a good idea bringin?everything out in the open.
将所有东西搬到空地可一目了然
This whole things all for nothin?
你明白我们意思吗？这于事无补
Theyre probably all three blind drunk in some Nogales whorehouse.
他们三人可能已醉卧奴基镇妓寨
Well, iftheyre dead drunk in Nogales, well know in 24 hours.
他们若醉倒于奴基镇
Surely we can put up with the man for one more day.
只不过是拖延多一天而已
No. Hes got this whole town so people are turnin?on each other.
不，我说不
他令全镇人挑起欲念
Whats the matter, Morgan? Anybody special turn on you?
摩根，什么事？
有人向你挑情吗？
- You want to spell that out, Drake? - Spell it yourself.
狄克，你想说出来吗？
Im not gonna jeopardize everything lve built here...
自己说吧
because some blond bitch in heat threw you out of bed.
我不想因为女人而名誉扫地
- Dont talk to me that way! - Ill talk to you any way I like!
妈的！别用这种口吻跟我说话
Ill say what I have to say while lm running this company.
我喜欢怎说你奈我如何？
Say it, but you could listen once in a while yourself!
我是公司负责人，有权发表言论
Whats the matter? Not gettin? your fair share ofthe profits?
说吧，你定会后悔的
摩根，你没分到合理的利润吗？
Its not the profits.
利润？那不是利润
This whole business has gone sour...
自从对付那邓肯警长后
since that deal with that former marshal, Duncan.
公司生意日渐衰弱
We had no choice in that matter and you know it.
你应知道，那时候我们别无选择
The big mistake was hiring that man Duncan in the fi rst place.
老友，等一会
最大的错误是当日雇用那邓肯
You did that all by yourself. Quiet! Shut up.
此事由你一人自把自为
We can trust one another.
收声，我们要互相信任
This whole town had a hand in what happened.
整个镇的人也插手那件事
Why do you think Bridges and the Carlin brothers...
你怎能期望史达斯及卡连兄弟…
kept their mouths shut all this time?
在这时候噤若寒蝉呢？
Same reason everybody else did in this town.
同一理由，全镇人也涉及此事
One hangs, we all hang.
一人被问吊，其他人也一样
Now, you just grit your teeth a little bit longer.
你要继续咬紧牙关
The gunfi ghter stays till I say otherwise. You understand?
直至那枪手离去，明白吗？
There it is, just like he said.
正如我所说
That strangers got everybody turnin?on everybody.
那神秘人令到各人混熟
Being put out in the middle ofthe night!
That man!
Right here. Folks, put your bags right here in the wagon.
老友，将袋放在车上
All right, folks. Just put your bags in the wagon.
对，就放在车上
- Whats going on here? - What the hell does it look like?
发生什么事？
Theyre emptying my whole hotel.
教士，你看像去哪里呢？
他们将我旅馆的物件搬清
Throwing out payin?guests, right into the street...
皆因要空出房间给新来的 保护者
just to make room for our new guardian angel.
他是喜欢独断独行的
He likes to be by himself, more or less.
You can see whos runnin?our town now.
你现在看见，是谁说没本领了
Hes sitting right over there, Mr Belding.
贝登先生，他就坐在那边
Ifyou dont like it...
若你不满意，何不向他直言
why dont you just go over there and tell him he cant?
Mordecai...
摩迪加， 你总有一天会被人践踏
someday soon someones going to step on your scrawny neck, you lizard.
When they do, youre going to be nothing but--
你会像沙漠的小洞，被人活埋
See here...
你不能要市民夜宿街头
you cant turn all these people out into the night.
It is inhuman, brother. Inhuman!
这是不人道的，兄弟，不人道
Im not your brother.
我并非你的兄弟
We are all brothers in the eyes of God.
在主的眼中，我们全是兄弟
All these people, are they your sisters and brothers?
这些人是你的兄弟姐妹吗？
They most certainly are!
大部分都是
Then you wont mind ifthey stay at your place, will ya?
你介意他们到你的地方逗留吗？
All right, folks, lets go. Put your bags here.
好了，我们走， 将行李放在这里
Friends, dont worry.
朋友们…别担心
We shall fi nd haven foryou in our own homes...
我们替你找个避难所
and it wont cost you one cent more than regular hotel rates.
收费绝不会贵过旅馆的房间
Thats ridiculous.
真荒谬
- My room ready? - Two connecting rooms.
我们房间已预备好吗？
The best in the hotel.
是旅馆最好的…两间相连房
One for entertaining your many new friends in town...
一间招待新朋友， 一间供你睡觉
and one for sleeping...
ifyour conscience lets you sleep.
若你良知容许你入寐的话
- I sleep just fi ne, maam. - Is that so?
我会睡得安宁的
是吗？
You care to see foryourself?
你不如关心自己吧
You tell Mrs Belding therell be two for supper.
通知贝登太太预备两份晚餐
I like chicken, fried.
我想吃烧鸡
And anything else?
还有其他吗？
Best bottle ofwine in town.
要一瓶镇内最好的酒
Remember: He wont be around forever, you little--
记住，他不会永远出现的…
Marshal.
警长
Help me, please. Help me.
救我呀！求你！救我呀
- What are you doing? - Let go! Youve got to stop this!
你要去哪里
放我走，你快停手
Let go of me!
现在不行
放我走
Damn you all to hell.
那你们全去死吧！
How did you get in here?
你是如何进来的？
You had your chance and you missed it.
原本你是有机会的，但已错过了
Youre hurting me. What do you want?
你弄伤我了，你想怎样？
Just a little pleasant female company for supper.
只是寻开心，找个女伴共膳
- You know what you are? - What?
知否你是什么？ 是什么？
- Youre an animal. - You have a way of bringing that out.
你是只禽兽
你会有机会拿出来的
Thankyou, but I dont eat with dogs.
多谢，但我不会跟一只狗共膳
You might, if its a dog that runs the pack.
你会的，若那只狗联群结队
- Give me halfan hour to get ready. - Youre ready right now.
给半小时让我去预备
I could be readier.
你已预备好了 要预备的更好
Halfan hour.
半小时
You know, actually, I eat like a bird.
其实我食量象小鸟般
Ive got it!
我知那贱人贺巴将它藏在仓库内
I knew that old bastard Hobart had it in a hole under the store.
- Look. But I got it. - Yeah, all the way from France.
终于给我找到了
对，是来自法国的佳酿
Stick a bent knife in that, get the cork out.
请你用弯刀将瓶塞拔出来
Do you have any special request for dessert?
要特定吃些什么甜品吗？
No, lve already taken care ofthat.
我已经安排好了
Cant fix that without a blacksmith or a vet. Maybe both.
要找铁匠或兽医处理，或者两者
Itll be hell fi ndin?either one out here.
在这地方怎能找到？
Ill tell you something, Stace.
史达斯，我告诉你一件事
I think weve been pushin?too hard.
我们实在催迫太紧了
Like as not, all three ofthese horses could have come up lame.
否则，三匹马也不会跛了
I feel pretty lame myself, not being on a horse 1 2 months in thatjail.
我坐牢一年，双腿也快跛了
Back off, Cole. Maybe we ought to leave you and the horse here.
走开，否则将你和马匹留在这里
Now, Stace, I didnt mean nothin?
史达斯，我不是有意的
He can ride double with me until we come across somebody.
在遇到人之前我俩可同骑一马
- Well all need fresh animals. - All right! But quit cryin?about it.
我们也要换几匹新的马
好的，但不要张扬
Ill tell you what, though.
我要告诉你，若被他们发现尸体
Soon as they fi nd those bodies...
theyre going to have a huntin?party out for us.
他们定会联群结队出来捕杀我们
And I want time to take one year of my life out of Lago...
我会花一年时间在拉高镇
before we move on.
How long is that going to take, you fi gure?
你看实际要多久？
A lifetime...
要半生时间对付其中部分人
for some ofem.
Youre out late, Mordecai.
摩迪加，你迟到了 什么？
Fornication and sins ofthe flesh.
通奸，侮辱肉体…
Thats whats going on under my roof right now while lm talking to you.
我跟你说话时他正在上面鬼混
That stranger has taken over my hotel...
那神秘人霸占我的旅馆…
and thrown good, honest, decent folk out into the night.
要善良诚实的人夜宿街头
Why didnt you stop him, Lewis? Youve got a gun.
你为何不阻止他？你有手枪的
Shut your fat mouth, Sam.
闭上你的肥嘴！
Were tired of giving you money for doing an incompetentjob.
我们付你酬劳你全不称职
- Dont you talk to me that way! - Gentlemen!
别用这口吻跟我说话
Please! Look at us!
各位先生，请看看我们
Sweet God, look whats happening to us!
亲爱的主， 请看我们发生什么事
Right, itsjust like the preacher says.
正如教士所说…
That strangers got everybody at each others throats.
神秘人令全镇人同一意向
Hes set himself up like a king.
他将自己制造成一个皇帝
Hes got you all snake-fascinated, every damn one ofyou.
他令你们神魂颠倒…
每个人也如是
This crazy picnic. Two hundred gallons of blood-red paint.
今次疯狂的野营
还有那二百加仑红油漆…
It couldnt be worse ifthe devil himself had ridden into Lago.
比魔鬼入侵拉高镇更可怕
Welcome to Lago, you son ofa bitch.
欢迎来到拉高镇，杂种！
Get out of here!
我们离开这里
God, what was that?
Im sorry.
Morg!
摩…
你要去哪里？
Where are you going? Morg? Take me with you!
摩，带我一起去
你最好带我一起去， 你要去哪里
You better take me with you!
Where are you going? Dont leave me here!
摩，别留下我，他会杀我的
Hell kill me!
走开！来，我们走！
Oh, no!
不！不！
我的旅馆，他答应过不会的…
My beautiful hotel. They promised me they wouldnt--
Ruined.
摧毁了
A total loss.
完全摧毁了
Didnt even touch my store.
我的店铺没有遭殃
I want you to watch that pilfering. I hold you responsible, Sheriff.
警长，你要替我看守防小偷
Im not your goddamn sheriff.
我已不再是你的警长了
Ill need one, two-- two up there.
我要派两个人留守这里
Ill need four boxes from you...
我需要从你那儿要四个箱子以及一些铁锹
and shovels from you, so these people can dig the holes.
Well, I thought perhaps we could--
让他们可以挖洞
我看，不如… 立即去！
- Right now! - Yeah. All right, everyone.
好的，各位…
Was you here? Did you see anything?
你在场吗？你目睹什么？
Somebody left the door open and the wrong dogs came home.
有人门户大开，让那些狗回家
是… 去拿铁链 是
Get the shovel, will ya?
I hope youre not going to blame us for Morgan Allens stupidity...
请你别责怪我们， 摩根愚昧无知
because the rest of us here have an agreement with you.
其余的人跟你有协议…
Right now I dont feel too agreeable.
我觉得你们不大合作
Well, maybe a little bonus will make you a little more appreciative.
或许给你少许奖赏会令你满意
- How little? - Five hundred a head.
少许是多少？
每个人头五百块
Five hundred an ear?
五百块一只耳朵
Done, done.
成交
$3,000?
三千元？ 他如此对待我的旅馆
You promised that son ofa bitch $3,000...
after what he did to my hotel?
你竟答应给那杂种三千元
Promisings one thing. Payings another.
答应了一件事必须付出代价
He mayjust catch a bullet.
他可能要接受一粒子弹
You and Lewis can grab shovels too.
你和路易士也要去拿铁链
I knew you were cruel, but I didnt know how faryou could go.
我知你残酷， 但不知竟如此残酷
You still dont.
你是不会知的
It doesnt matter to you.
这事影响不到你
I dont know where youre going to sleep now. Bodies everywhere.
不知你会在哪里睡觉
All the rooms are ruined except for our room.
尸体遍地，除了我们的房间外
其余房间已被摧毁
Wait. Wait a minute.
等一会，不！
Oh, no!
不…放过我
Let go! Let go! Lewis!
Lewis, dontjust stand there.
路易士，别袖手旁观，放我走
Let go of me!
Stop! Look, you dont need me. Let go!
你用不着我的，放过我
Let go of me!
放我走
- What are you going to do with those? - Defend myself.
你用这剪刀做什么？
自卫
Against what?
要对付什么？
Its no secret what you did to Callie Travers.
你跟歌莉做过的事已不是秘密
- Did? - The other day in the stable.
做过的事？
那天在马槽里
As I recall, she enjoyed that quite a bit.
我想起来了，她很享受
I promise you, I wont.
我告诉你，我是不会的
- You flatteryourself, lady. - I flatter myself?
你在骗自己
我在骗自己？
Id love to oblige you, but a mans got to get his rest sometime.
我想为你效劳 但男人是要休息的
Oblige me?
为我效劳？
But ifyou come back in about a half hour...
我告诉你，若你半小时后回来
Ill see what I can do, all right?
我看，我定可做得到
Why, you low-down, stinking, son ofa--
你这下流无耻之徒…
Have you ever heard the name Jim Duncan?
你有听过吉姆・邓肯这名字吗？
Ive heard a lot ofthings. Why?
我听过很多东西，什么事？
He was town marshal here.
他以前是这里的军官
Hes lying out there in an unmarked grave.
现在躺在一个无名的墓穴里
They say the dead dont rest without a marker ofsome kind.
人们说在无名的墓穴内 是不安息的
Do you believe that?
你相信吗？
- What makes you think I care? - I dont know.
你怎会觉得我介意这些
他令本镇居民害怕陌生人
Hes the reason this towns afraid ofstrangers.
I was going to warn you about that. Pretty funny.
我要向你提出警告，真有趣
Whats funny?
什么有趣事？
You ask me that in a blown-up hotel...
你竟在一间被摧毁的旅馆内…
with seven dead men to your credit already?
有七个被你累死的人前
I wasjust stopping by for a bottle ofwhiskey...
我只不过路经此地…
and a nice hot bath.
想喝杯威士忌，洗个热水浴
All right. Ifyou say so.
随便你怎说
You dont believe me?
你不相信我？
Mister, whateveryou say is fi ne with me.
你说什么，也不关我事
Be careful.
你要小心
Youre a man who makes people afraid, and thats dangerous.
一个令人恐怖的男人 是很危险的
Its what people know about themselves inside...
一个了解自己的人才会恐怖
that makes them afraid.
I dont know ifwe shouldnt mark the grave somehow.
应否在墓碑上刻上名字呢？
Sam?
I dont see any need.
我看不必，反正无人会来哭坟
Aint likely anybodys gonna cry over em anyhow.
You know what to do.
你知应该做什么吗？
Yes, sir, captain.
是，长官
All right.
大家拿油刷来开工
Everybody grab a brush and start in.
You mean, you want the whole place painted?
要将所有地方漆上红油？
- Everything. - You cant possibly mean the church.
全部要
要将教堂也漆上红油？
I mean especially the church.
尤其是教堂
All right. Ill paint ifyou say weve got to...
既然你要求，我们干吧
but when we get done, this place is gonna look like hell.
完成后，这地方会像地狱般
[地狱]
Hello, Lewis.
路易士
I want you to go to that meeting with me, Sarah. Its very important.
我想你去参加会议， 是很重要的
No.
不，现在不去，永远也不去
Not now, not ever.
They are still your neighbours!
他们仍算是你的邻居啊！
Yes, theyre my neighbours, and they make me sick.
他们是我的邻居， 他们令我恶心
Hiding behind words like faith, peace and trust.
表面说什么忠心、 和平、互信
Good words. Damn good words.
好词藻，好堂煌的词藻
- But we hid a murder behind them. - Will you never understand, woman?
我们将杀手收藏在他们背后
你仍不明白，这是迫不得已的
That wasnt anything we wanted to do.
When Duncan found out the mine was on government property...
当邓肯发觉金属 矿属于政府所有时
it wasjust a technicality, really, but he was determined to turn us in.
他竟告发我们
Wouldnt listen to reason.
完全不听因由
Is that why?
这是真正的原因吗？
- Is that really why it happened? - Dont you see, Sarah?
They would have closed down the mine.
莎拉，他们会将矿地封闭
Do you know what wouldve happened to this town then?
之后， 这个镇会变成什么模样呢？
It wouldve been the end ofeverything weve worked on.
我们以前的功夫将会完蛋
All of it, all of us. And you too, wife.
是全部，所有人，包括你， 老婆
有时候我们必须做对人有益的事
Sometimes we have to do whats necessary to do...
for the good ofeverybody.
- Thats the price of progress. - And whats the price ofa human life?
这是进步的代价
那么，生命的价值是什么？
Askyour good friends ifthey know that.
去问你的好友吧， 若他们晓得
Your damn conscience.
你做人太执着了
Its sure taken a hell ofa while to botheryou.
就当我令你添上麻烦吧
Im packing to leave, Lewis.
我会收拾行李离去
I wont be coming back.
我将不会回来
Thats Morg Allen, or whats left of him.
他是摩根.阿伦， 他有什么事？
Well, now, whats he doing ridin?around like that?
他怎会这样骑马的？
Hes come back to pay us back for some jail time that was rightfully his...
他要补偿我们受过的牢狱之苦
only he dont know it yet.
他是应有此报的，可能他仍未知
Stacey, help me.
史达斯，救我呀
My arm. Help me.
Help me, Stacey.
救我呀，史达斯
Im curious, Morg.
摩根，我感到疑惑…
You helped them railroad us, and then youve got the balls...
你帮他们令我们能身陷牢狱
to come down here and ask us for a favour?
现在竟然到来乞求我们救你？
Goddamn if I dont admire you.
你实在值得我们敬仰
Do something about my arm, Stacey.
史，帮我治疗手伤吧
I am doing something, Morg.
我会的，摩根
Im sitting here watching you bleed to death.
我会袖手旁观， 看着你流血身亡
史，拉高镇已完全变了
Things have changed in Lago.
You need me.
你会需要我的
I gotta tell you about it.
我会详细的告诉你
我会详细的告诉你的
From the looks ofyour arm, Morg...
凭你手臂的伤势，我看的出…
youve run your welcome out in Lago, and ours too.
你在镇内不受欢迎， 而我们也是
The boys want to know how were gonna get 1 2 months?back pay...
我和他俩想知道…
如何补偿过去一年的损失
and everything else thats owed us?
要将欠我们的一切讨回来
- Stacey, for Gods sake. - No. For our sake.
史达斯，要靠天了
不要靠我们自己
You can help us, and you can help yourselftoo.
你要帮我们，亦要帮自己
Just give me the combination to that big iron box in your office...
你只需将夹万密码告诉我们…
and me and the boys will sneak in there...
是放在你办公室内的夹万
我们能会静静地潜入去…
real quiet like, take whats ours...
拿取我们应得的， 余数会全给你
bring you the rest, or leave it there safe and sound.
又或者留在夹万内， 由你决定
First, ofcourse, well fix up your arm...
首先，当然会替你疗伤
and set you over there in the shade...
然后将你安置在阴凉的地方
with a nice canteen full ofwater.
You no-good, worthless son ofa bitch.
你这无耻之徒
Youre probably right about that.
你说的对
Give me that combination, Morg.
将密码告诉我
I wouldnt give you the combination to the gates of hell.
我会将通往地狱的密码告诉你
Dog!
Sure had a lot of blood left in him, didnt he?
看来他还有很多血可以流
Two sticks ofdynamite will take care ofthat iron box anyway.
反正用炸药也可以炸开 不必他了
We dont need him.
- Dan, you hit? - I dont know.
是你开枪吗？ 我不知
I dont think so. Damn near tore my leg off!
不是我，差点射中我的腿
- Who the hell is that? - Must be Dave Drake.
究竟他是谁？
一定是狄克
What the hell did you hit?
你射中了什么？
- Keep shooting, damn it! - He shot my ear off!
继续开枪
他射中了我的耳朵
- Somebody up theres playing games. - He shot my ear off!
有人在上面玩把戏
他射中我的耳朵
He couldve shot your damn head off! Now get down!
他应射中你的头，快伏下
Dave, is that you?
狄克，是你吗？
Come on out! Well settle this.
出来吧，我们摆平这事
Morg was almost dead anyway from that arm!
摩根手臂受伤，快要死了
I just put him out of his misery!
我只不过帮他解除痛苦
Ill kill you!
我要杀死你
You son ofa bitch, lll kill you!
你这杂种，我要杀死你
Come down out ofthere, you bastard! lll cut your heart out!
你出来，我要割掉你的心
Dont go up there. There might be more dynamite.
不如到上面吧，可能有些炸药
Ill kill him, whoever it was up there.
我要去捉他，不管他是谁
Ill kill every man in Lago!
我要杀尽所有拉高镇的人
The guests are on their way to the party. Gather all the people together.
我们的贵宾正在途中， 大家集合
Right, captain! All right, men, get that sign up!
知道…挂起这横额
Come on! Theyre coming!
他们来了
All right, everybody, get a little move on!
各位，动身吧！
I want you up in that tower. First sign ofdust, you ring the bell.
我想你登上这塔
见到尘土飞扬便敲响警钟
Are you sure this is gonna be all right?
你肯定可行？
Its gonna be all right.
一定可以
Hes back! Hes here! lts time to get ready.
他们回来了，是时候预备了
Whats the matter with everybody? Waitll we gun em down.
大家有什么问题？
我们能定可以开枪射低他们… 砰…
All right, everybody, I think were expected outside.
我们到外面等
I just hope that shooter we hired is feelin?up to snuff.
希望雇用的枪手能消灭他们
Dont worry. Hell be fi ne.
别担心，他可做到的
Lets go.
我们出发
先生，我们能放假吗？ 不
Senor, can we come to the fiesta?
No.
I want everybody to have plenty ofthose.
我希望各人有足够的弹药
不是要出去吗？
Aint it about time we got out there, huh?
Theres plenty oftime.
还有很多时间
But theyll be here any damn minute.
但他们会随时到来
I think Sams right. We ought to.
我看森姆可应付的
What about after?
之后呢？之后如何处理他们呢？
What about after we do it?
What do we do then?
之后怎办？
Then you live with it.
你可跟他们一起生活
Where you gonna be? Are you gonna take the fi rst shot?
你去了哪里？ 第一枪应由你去开
Are you gonna get Stacey Bridges fi rst?
要先射死史达斯吗？
Or maybe youre gonna get all three by yourself?
抑或要亲手解决他们三人？
- When are you gonna give the signal? - Im not.
你何时会发出讯号？
我不会，由你去发
You are.
You old people, move outta here!
你们这些老家伙，快离开这里
Here they come!
他们来了
[地狱]
“欢迎回家孩子们”
来吧
Fire!
开枪！…
Fire! Fire!
Get em!
射他们！
Dont shoot!
不…不要开枪
A party?
开派对吗？
Welcome-home party, huh?
欢迎我回家的派对吗？
Well, heres to your party.
送给你的
Give me another bottle.
多拿一瓶给我
Give me another bottle!
多拿一瓶给我！
- Well, now the partys over. - Let go of me!
派对结束了
史达斯 放我走
Look what I found in the bushes!
看我在树丛中找到什么？
Stacey, it was always you.
史达斯，一直都是你
Thats why Morg Allen hated you.
这是阿伦憎恨你的原因
He knew how much I loved you.
你知我一直深爱你
Yeah, I bet you just cried yourself to sleep every night...
你晚上睡觉时有哭吗？
thinking about me in that territorial prison.
你想过我在监狱内的生活吗？
But I did. I really did!
有，我真的有
Yeah, well, I can see it all now.
我现在完全明白了
You lying there in Morg Allens bed...
你躺在阿伦床上狂呼造爱
just a-cryin?and a-humpin?
Oh, no!
不！…
Give me that bottle.
拿酒给我
- Cole, go and get the horses ready. - You got it, Stace.
高雨，去预备马匹 知道
史，你要带我跟你走吗？
Youre going to take me with you, arent you?
I can do better than you in a four-bit fancy house.
我会将你安置在一间四房豪宅
- You still here? - Goddamn right lm still here!
你仍在这里？
对，我仍在这里
I wanna know who them sons of bitches was that ambushed us.
我想知道谁在埋伏
Thats what were gonna fi nd out right now.
我们能马上会知道
Who are you?
你是谁？
Dont hit me!
Dont hit me, please!
Come on, Stacey. Lets get outta here.
史，我们离开这里 闭嘴
Shut up!
Everybody out.
所有人出来，所有人出来！
Everybody out!
- Out! - Move!
走！快走！
Go on. Get out!
快点！走！…
Hurry up in there. Move!
- Get in there. - Hold it right there!
站住，进去！
Dynamite!
Stacey, the goddamn horses are gone!
史达斯，那些马匹走了
Go on. Go on!
继续！
Help me.
救我！救我呀！
Help me!
Who are you?
你是谁？
Im just about done here.
我只是在这里把它弄完
- I never did know your name. - Yes, you do.
我从来未知你的姓名
他知道
Take care.
多保重
Yes, sir, captain.
是，长官
吉姆・邓肯警长在此安息